Guide to The Peter Dougherty Collection 1965 - 2001 MSS 213
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Audio
  - Subseries A: Audio, 1776-1785
    - Cale/ Roxy singles/ Patti Smith - Horses, undated (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0166)
      Side A (CALE, Roxy B-Sides & Hot Singles) Helen of Troy, Guts, Heartbreak Hotel, The Ballad of Cable Hogue, Leaving It Up To You/(ROXY): Virginia, Plain the Number, Pajamarama, Pride of the Pain, [2 M. B.], Remake/Remodel, For Your Pleasure (live), Eno- The Lion Sleeps Tonight (cut)
      Container Annotation: Cale Nov 30th 1975 singles- [Alister] - P.D. (212)5449224.
      Side B (PATTI SMITH HORSES): Gloria, Redondo Beach, Birdland, Free Monday, Kimberly, Break It Up, Land, Elegie.
      Container Annotation: Vocal- Patti Smith, guitar- Lenny Kaye, Piano-Richard Sohl, Bass,Guitra - Ivan Kral
    - Erasers - May 16 & 28, 1977, CBGB, May 1977 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0167)
      Side A: #7, Jody, Marc in Leather, Come Out in the Streets, I Don't Love Anyone, Everybody's Got a Dog, 1977-, Jody, No fun, Funtime, Come Out in the Streets
      Side B: Marc in Leather, Everybody's Got a Dog
    - John Cale & Friends, July 26, 27th 1976, July 26, 1976 - July 27, 1976 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0168)
      Side A (July 26): Ghost Story, Buffalo Ballet, You Know More Than I Know, Guts, Waiting For the Man, Close Watch, [Track Unknown], Gun --> Pablo Picasso, Cable Hogue
      Side B: Babe What Ya Want Me To Do/ (July 27) Ghost Story, Buffalo Ballet, You Know More Than I Do, Darling, Guts, Waiting For My Man, Gun --> Pablo Picasso.
      Container Annotation: J. Cale- vocal, guitar, piano. P. Smith- vocal, guitar? D. Byrne- guitar. A. Lanier -piano, guitar, Mick Ronson - guitar
    - Nico BBC/ Paris 72, 1972 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0169)
      Sides A and B: Secret Sides, [Transfer of Love], We've Got the Gold, the End, Pale Blue Eyes, Black Angel Death, Heroin
    - Lou Reed live Oct 6 1974, October 6, 1974 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0170)
      Side A: Intro-Sweet Jane, Vicious, Ride Sally Ride, Heroin, Animal Talk, Sally Can't Dance, Walk on the Wild Side
      Side B: NY Stars, Kill Your Sons, White Light/ White Heat, [Gooden Mr. Cabe], Rock & Roll
    - Lou Reed, Dec 26 1972, December 26, 1972 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0171)
    - Judy Nylon w/ Nolan, Ed/ Dead Boys w/ J. Nolan, May 3, 1978 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0172)
      Side A: Trial by Fire, Whem I'm Bored, All I Want, Breakdown
      Side B: Time's Up Looking For a Kiss
    - John Cale & Friends July 26, 27 1976 Lower Manhattan Ocean Club, July 1976 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0173)
      Side A (July 26): Ghost Story, Buffalo Ballet*, You Know More Than I Know, Guts, Waiting For the Man*, I Keep a Close Watch, The Jeweler -->, Gun -->, Pablo Picasso, Cable Hogue
      Side B: Babe What Ya Want Me To Do?/(July 27th) Ghost Story, Buffalo Ballet, You Know More Than I Know Darling, I Need You, Guts, Waiting For the Man, Gun -->, Pablo Picasso, Babe What You Want Me To Do?
      Containe Annotation: J.Cale-vocal, piano, guitar. M.Ronson- guitar. D. Byrne - guitar, B. vocal (27th), A. Lainer - guitar, piano, b. vocal (27th), * (26th P. Smith-Voice)
    - Television Demo, Eno & Williams 1974/ Cale with Lou, Patti, David Byrne- July 20 1976, Ocean Club, 1974/1976 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0174)
      Side A (Television Demos): Prove It, Friction, Venus De Milo, Marquee Moon, Double Exposure, Fire Engine (live), Blank Generation (live)/ Heartbreakers Demo 1975: Love Comes in Spurts, I Wanna Be Loved, Blank Generation
      Side B (Cale): Ghost Story, Buffalo Ballet, You Know More Than I Know, Guts, Waiting For My Man, [Track Unknown] -->, Gun -->, Pablo Picasso, Babe What Ya Want Me To Do?
    - Lou Reed - Live Felt For, April 26, 1975 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0175)
      Side A: Sweet Jane, I Wanna Be Black, Coney Island Baby, You Can Dance, I'm Waiting for My Man, Heroin, Berlin, Lady Ray
      Side B: Uptown Dirt, Walk on the Wild Side, Kicks, Complete This Story Now, Rock N Roll
      Container Annotation: Lou- guitar, vocal, Doug Yule- guitar, b. vocal
    - Ramones Live Max's Aug 6th 1976, August 1976 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0176)
      Side A: Loudmouth, Beat on the Brats, Blitzkrieg Bop, Suzie is a Head Banger, Glad to See Ya Go, Gimmie Gimmie Shock Treatment, 53rd & 3rd, Boyfriend, Havana Affair, Listen to My Heart, Calif Sun, Judy is a Punk, I Don't Walk Around with You, I'm a Nazi baby, Today Ya Love
      Side B: Basement, Sniff Some Glue, Blitzkrieg Bop, I Don't Wanna Be a Pinhead No Nore, Chainsaw, Listen to My Heart, Baby Sitter, Commando, Oh Oh I Love Her So, Let's Dance, Walk Around, Nazi Baby, I'm Gonna Kill that Girl, Judy is a Punk, California Sun
    - Ramones CBGB May 15, 76/ LA Roxy August [] 76 -Radio-, May 1976, August 1976 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0177)
      Side A: Basement, Sniff Glue, Blitz Bop, Swallow My Pride, Glad to See Ya Go, Chainsaw, Listen to My Heart, Babysitter, 53rd and 3rd, Havana Affair, Let's Dance, Judy
      Side B: Loudmouth, Beat on the Brats, Blitzkrieg Bop, Glad to See Ya Go, 53rd and 3rd, Boyfriend, Havana Affair, Calif Sun, Judy, I Don’t Wanna Walk, Nazi/ Void-oids - Down at the RnRoll Club
    - Ramones Live Max's. Aug 7 1976 stereo, PD & McKim. Feb 4th 1977 Mono dolby, 1976/1977 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0178)
      Side A: Loudmouth, Brats, Blitz Bop, I Remember You, Glad to See Ya Go, Shock Treatment, 53rd and 3rd, Boyfriend, Havana Affair, Listen to My Heart, Calif Sun, Judy is a Punk, Walk around with You, Nazi Baby, Today Ya Love, Tomorrow the World
      Side B: Loudmouth, Brat, Blitz Bop, I Remember You, Glad to See Ya Go, ShockTreatment, 53rd and 3rd, Goodboy, Headbanger, Boyfriend, Havana Affair, Listen to My Heart, Calif Sun, Judy is a Punk, I Don’t Wanna Walk around with You
    - Ramones - Max's October 8th 1976 (early) October 9th 1976 (late show) (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0179)
      Sides and B: Loudmouth, Brats, I Remember You, Glad to See You Go, Shock Treatment, Kill That Girl, Sniff Glue, 53rd and 3rd, Boyfriend, Judy, Havana Affair, Calif Sun, Walk Around, Nazi Baby -- Kill That Girl, Glad to See Ya Go, Gimmie Gimmie Shock Treatment, Commando, Sniff Glue, Suzy is a Head Banger, Havana Affair, Listen to My Heart, Calif Sun, Judy is a Punk, I Don’t Wanna Walk around with You, Nazi Baby, -- Chainsaw, Let's Dance
    - Ramones -all new- La Peste Hurrah July 4 1978/ My Father's Place July 5 1978 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0180)
      Side A: Rockaway Beach, Lobotomy, Blitz Bop, I Don't Want You
      Side B: Glad to See Ya Go, Shock T, Somethin To Do, Wanted Every
    - Ramones Oct 30, 1977 CBGB early show/ late, a grape tape (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0181)
      Sides A and B: Loudmouth, Brats, Blitz Bop, I Remember You, Glad to See Ya Go, Teenage Lobotomy, Kill That Girl, Sheena, Rockaway Beach, Commando, Here Today- Gone Tomorrow, Surfin Bird, Cretin Hop, Listen to My Heart, Calif Sun, Walk Around, Pinhead, 53rd and 3rd, Carbona, Nazi Baby, Basement, Sniff Glue
    - Ramones CBGB 1st set June 10th 77/ Nervous Rex -Max's Jan 15, 1978 Miriam Linna, 1977/1978 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0182)
      (June 10th 77) Duplicators, Stop All Dancing, Dubrule 1250, Index, No Regrets Sort Of, Rachel in the Ruins, She's Not There, Leave Me Alone, Fun with Numbers
    - Ramones 6-9-77 CBGB 3 early 24 late, the Grape, 1977 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0183)
      Side A: Swallow, Shock Treatment, I Don’t Care, Loudmouth, Ramona, Blitz Bop, I Remember You, Glad to See Ya Go, Teenage, Kill That Girl, Carbona Not Glue, Sheena is a Punk, Babysitter, Havana Affair, Pinhead, Sniff Glue, Nazi Baby
      Side B: Goodboy, Chainsaw, Calif Sun, 53rd & 3rd, Suzi, Love is the Drug, Tokyo Joe, This is Tomorrow, The In Crowd, A Hard Rain's Gonna Fall, Price of Love
    - Ramones LIVE July 13, 1976 My father's place, McKim (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0184)
      Loudmouth
      General note
      The final two minutes of track one are disrupted by tape malformation, which causes variable speed and stop/start. The glitches happen about every two seconds for this segment.
    - Ramones June 10th 76 Max's, 1976 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0185)
      Side A: Loudmouth, Brats, Blitzkrieg Bop, I Remember You, Glad to See Ya Go, Shock Treatment, 53rd & 3rd, Boyfriend, Havana Affair, Listen to My Heart, Calif Sun, Judy, Walk Away, Nazi Baby
      Side B: Basement, Sniff Glue, Glad to See Ya Go, Chainsaw, Listen to My Heart, Babysitter, Oh Oh I Love Her So, Commando, Let's Dance, Judy is a Punk, Walk Away, Nazi Baby-
    - Lenny K Xmas, CBGB xmas 79/ Mac, Cambodia Benefit Cooper Union, 1979 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0186)
      Content: None
    - Modern Lovers- Live at the Kitchen NY March 1975/ Ramones- Live 9/14/75 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0187)
      Modern Lovers: This Little Light of Mine, Rock Island Line, She's My Girlfriend, Cum Bi Ya, Goodninght Baby, No Need to Fear My Honest Dear, She Loves You Johnathan, Blue Suede Shoes, Don’t Worry Baby, Born Too Late, Dreamland Girlfriend, New Teller (2nd time), Hi Friend We Still Love You, Roadrunner
    - Ramones May 15th 1976 CBGB late, Donk's rock concert/ "Ramones" LP (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0188)
      Side A: (Ramones May 15 '76/Sets I & II) Sheena, Loudmouth, Brats, Blitz Bop, Heart, Calif Sun, Jusy, Glad to See Ya Go, Shock Treatment, Rockaway Beach, Commando-- Loudmouth, Beat on Brats, BlitzBop, I Remember You, Glad to See Ya Go, ShockTreatment
      Side B: (Ramones LP) Blitzkrieg Bop, Beat on the Brats, Judy is a Punk, I Wanna Be Your Boyfriend, Chain Saw, Now I Wanna Sniff Some Glue, Go Down to the Basement, [Lordern to] Havana Affair, Listen to My Heart, 53rd & 3rd, Let's Dance, I Don’t Wanna Walk Around with You, Nazi Baby- Today [Yal-ow]
      Container Annotation on Inside of Label for Side B ("Television" crossed out on physical tape for Side B) (Ramones Live May 15th CBGB Television): Fire Engine, Friction, Hard on Love, Blank Generation, Psychotic rxn, UFO, Marquee Moon, Prove it (cut)
    - Talking Heads/ Blondie/ Ramones LIVE at CBGB July 18th 1975 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0189)
      Side A: Building on Fire, Artist's Only, Warning Sign, No Compassion. BLONDIE: In the Flesh, Moonlight Drive, Charlotte the Harlot, Platinum Blonde, Man Over Board.
      Side 2: RAMONES I Don’t Wanna Go Down in the Basement, Beat on the Brats, Let's Dance, 53rd and 3rd, Havana Affair, Calif Sun, Judy is a Punk. [TALKING HEADS] I Don’t Wanna, Girls Wanna Be with the Girls with Our Love, Psycho Killer, I'm Not in Llove. [RAMONES] I Don’t Wanna Walk away with You, Nazi Baby, Today Ya Love.
      Container Annotation: David Byrne- guitar, vocals, Tina Wamouth- bass, Chris Frantz- drums
    - Television at Mother's Oct 1975/ Ramones July 18 1975 at CBGB's (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0190)
      Side A: (Television at Mothers) Fire Engine, Judy Said, Marquee Moon, Iron Curtain, Friction, Breakin My Heart
      Side B: (Ramones) Basement, Beat on the Brat, Let's Dance, 53rd & 3rd, Havana Affair, Gonna Kill That Girl, California Sun, Judy is a Punk, I Don’t Wanna Walk away with You, Nazi
    - Ramones LIVE at Max's Aug 7, 1976 STEREO (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0191)
      Loudmouth, Beat on the Brat, Blitzkrieg Bop, I Remember You, Glad to See Ya Go, Gimmie Gimmie Shock Treatment, 53rd & 3rd, I Wanna Be Your Boyfriend, Havana Affair, Listen to My Heart, California Sun, Judy is a Punk, I Don’t Wanna Walk around with You, Nazi
    - Tom Verlaine/ Bloomsbury Theatre 2nd show, undated (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0192)
      Container Annotation: Both sides/ some other crap near end side A
    - Bruce Springsteen - Greetings from Asbury Park/Television Aug 8 1975 CBGB (copy) (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0193)
    - Television, Bottom Line 7/29/78 late show, 1978 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0194)
      Side A: Fire Engine, Glory, Grip of Love, Foxhole, Dream's Dreamer, Aint That Worth Nothing, Friction, Prove it, Marquee Moon, Kingdom Come, Satisfaction, *Psychotic Reaction, *
      Side B (no denotation)
    - Television/ Z/ Syncopaticon 8/31/77, 1977 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0195)
      Side A: Fire Engine, O Mi Amore, Adventure, Foxhole, Breakin in My Heart, I Don’t Care
      Side B: Poor Circulation, Kingdom Come, Psychotic Reaction
      Tape Length: unknown
    - Tom Verlaine PEP Lounge Oct 13th 1981 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0196)
      Sides A and B: Kingdom Come, Red Leaves, Souvenir of a Dream, Mile From You, Breakin in My Heart, Glory
    - Television Live at CBGB March 12, 1976 with the MONG (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0197)
      Side A: Kingdom Come (contd), Fire Engine, Venus de Milo, Torn Curtain, Little Johnny Jewel, Friction, Prove it, Knockin on Heaven's Door, Marquee Moon
      Side B: Oh mi Amore, Poor Circulation, Elevation, Let Me Out, Grip of Love, I Don’t Care
    - Television/ Talking Heads March 13, 1976 at the Kitchen (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0198)
      Side A (Television March 12): Foxhole, Kingdom Come, Psychotic Reaction (encore). TALKING HEADS: Artists Only, First Week/Last Week, I'm Not in Love, Love is Like a Building on Fire, Who Is It?
      Side B: Thank You For Sending Me an Angel, Sugar on My Tongue, Warning Sign, Girls w/ Girls, Psycho Killer, In My Heart, I Wish You Wouldn’t Say That, Stay Hungry, I Wanna Live, Tentative Decisions, No Compassion
      Container annotation: David Byrne- guitar, vocal, Chris Frantz- drums, vibes. Tina Weymouth-bass, occ guitar.
    - Television, Bottom Line June 11, 1978 early show, Pistols Jan 14 1978 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0199)
      Side A: Dreamer's Dreamer, Venus, Fristion, Pistols 1-14-78 part III
      Side B: Knockin, Marquee Moon, See No Evil (encore), Satisfaction (encore), No Feelings, Problems
    - Television 8 April 2001/ Camber Sands -A.T.P. (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0200)
    - Television/ Live June 15th 1975 CBGB (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0201)
      Side A: Fire Engine, Prove it, Poor Circulation, Friction, Breakin My Heart, Shirts, Surprise Package, Mr Blues
      Side B: I Don’t Care, Venus de Milo 95, Little Johnny Jewel 225, Foxhole 360, Marquee Moon 490, Double Exposure
      Container annotation: TV-guitar, vocal. Richard Lloyd, guitar. Billy Fecca-drums. Fred Smith-bass.
    - Television - My Father's Place, May 24, 1976 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0202)
      Side A: See No Evil (Sound check), I Don’t Care (Sound check), See No Evil, Prove It, Let Me Out, Friction, I Don’t Care, Knockin on Heaven's Door, Marquee Moon [Door]
      Side B: 7. cont'd, 8. Poor Circulation, 9. Venus de Milo, 10. Little Johnny Jewel, 11. Elevation, 12. Kingdom Come
      Container annotation: Recorded by Jackie E
    - Television Feb 15th 1975 CBGB (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0203)
      Side A: Psychotic Reaction, UFO, Foxhole*, Blank Generation, Marquee Moon, Double Exposure
      Side B: Fire Engine, Prove It, Friction, Venus de Milo, Poor Circulation, Hard on Love.
      Object Annotation: Side A: Roxy Music For Your Pleasure Side B: V.U. -Loaded
    - Television June 15th 1975 CBGB 1st with Fred Smith/ August 8th 1975 RnR fest (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0204)
      Side 1: Fire Engine, Prove It, Poor Circulation, Friction, Breakin in My Heart, I Don’t Care*, Venus de Milo, Little Johnny Jewel*, Foxhole*
      Side 2: Marquee Moon, Double Exposure*, Fire Engine, Prove It*, Poor Circulation, Little Johnny Jewel
    - Television/ Patti Smith/ Live March 22nd 1975, March 22, 1975 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0205)
      Side A: TELEVISION: Marquee Moon, Birds (Lloyd), Poor Circulation, Foxhole
      Side B: Hard on Love. PATTI SMITH: Captured by the Game
      Container Annotation: Patti Smith-vocals. Lenny Kaye-guitar. Richard Sohl. Ivan Kral-guitar. Property of P. Dougherty (212)5449224
    - Television/ The Mumps live Feb 22nd 1975 at CBGBs, February 22, 1975 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0206)
      Side A (Television): Psychotic Reaction, UFO, Foxhole, Blank Generation, Marquee Moon, Double Exposure
      Side 2 (Mumps): You Gotta Be Stupid, You Should Have Seen His Face Before the Accident, Night Owl, Back on the Street, Photogenia, Muscle Boys
      Container Annotation: Richard Hell-bass. Tom Verlaine-guitar. Richard Lloyd-guitar. Billy Ficca-drums. Lance Loud-Vocal. Christain-piano. Property of P. Dougherty (212)5449224
    - Television Live Feb 22nd 1975 at CBGBs, February 22, 1975 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0207)
      Side A: Push it or Pull it (Fire Engine), Friction, Prove it, Arms of Venus de Milo, Poor Circulation
      Side B: Hard on Love. +Roxy Music+: Out of the Blue, Thrill of it All. [swastika symbol]Hot Tuna[swastika symbol]: Come Back Baby
      Container Annotation: Rich Lloyd-v+guitar. Rich Hell-bass. Billy Ficca-drums. Tom Verlaine-vocal, guitar. Property of Peter Dougherty (212)544-9224
    - Talking Heads/ Television 8/2, undated (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0208)
      Side A (Talking Heads): The Girls Wanna Be with the Girls, With Our Love, Love is Like a Building on Fire, Tentative Decisions, Psycho Killer, I'm Not in Love, Artists Only, Warning Sign
      Side B (Television): Fire Engine, Prove it, Poor Circulation, Little Johnny Jewel, Friction, Hard On Love (soft)- Kingdom Come
      Container Annotation: David Byrne- Vocal, Guitar. Tina-bass. Chris Frantz- Drums. / Television TV- Guitar, Vocal. R Lloyd- Guitar, Billy Fecca- Drums. Fred Smith - Bass
    - 1- Television March 12, 1976- Live at CBGB aith MONG (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0209)
      Side A: Fire Engine, Venus de Milo, Torn Curtain, Little Johnny Jewel, Friction, Prove It, Knockin on Heaven's Door, Marquee Moon
      Side B: Oh Me Amore, Poor Circulation, Elevation, Let Me out
    - 2- Television: March 12, May 26, '76. Both Live at CBGB, 1976 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0210)
      TV March 12/ May 26-
      Side A: Grip of Love, I Don't Care, Foxhole, Kingdom Come, Psychotic Reaction (encore), See No Evil, I Don't Care
      Side B: Friction, Little Johnny Jewel, Elevation, Marquee Moon
    - Television Dec 30, 1976 CBGB, December 30, 1976 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0211)
      Side A: Fire Engine 3:30, Venus de Milo 3. Elevation 4. Little Johnny Jewel 5. I Don't Care 6. Friction 7. Marquee Moon
      Side B: See No Evil, Prove It, Adventure
    - Television July 4th 1976 Live at the Lower Manhattan Ocean Club on Chamber Street Un advertised- Strange gig- One set no breaks, July 4, 1976 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0212)
      Side A: See No Evil, Poor Circulation, Prove it, Little Johnny Jewel, I Don't Care, Marquee Moon, Friction
      Side B: Knockin on Heaven's Door, Kingdom Come, Oh Me Amore (encore)
    - Television 4 December '92 NYC Academy, December 4, 1992 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0213)
    - Television July 29, 1976 CBGB Stereo Set #1 Only, [McKim]- assistant (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0214)
      Side A: Fire Engine, Poor Circulation, Elevation, Oh me Amore, Venus de Milo, Knockin on Heaven's Door
    - John Cale Xmas 1976/ Television Dec 27th CBGBs (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0215)
      Side A: Helen of Troy, You Know More Than, Darling, Guts, Leaving it Up to You, Fear, Gun--> Pablo Picasso, Cable Hogue
      Side B: Little Johnny Jewel, I Don't Care, Friction, Knockin' on Heaven's Door, Marquee Moon, Satisfaction (encore)
      Access CD available by appointment only. Please request parts 1 and 2.
    - Television-March 20th 75 Live at CBGB's/ Television Jan 17, 1975 at CBGB's (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0216)
      Sides A and B: Venus de Milo, (I Belong To) the Blank Generation, Friction, (I Look At You and I set a) Double Exposure, Marquee Moon, Poor Circulation, Birds (Lloyd), Foxhole, Hard on Love (hard), Blank Generation (crossed out) Psychotic Reaction, Marquee Moon, Prove It, UFO, Poor Circulation, Double Exposure, Breakin' My Heart- (encore), Hard on Love (hard)
      Container Annotation: Tom Verlaine- Vocal, guitar; Richard Hell- Vocal, Bass; Richard Lloyd- Rhythm Guitar; Billy Fecca- Drums
    - Early Television - Summer '74 Max's/ Followed by Mother's 10/18/75, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0217)
      Side 1 (Television at Max's 1974): Psychotic Reaction, Excitement, Double Exposure, Venus de Milo, Fuck Rock 'n' Roll, Prove It, Change Your Channel, Fire Engine, Judy Said
      Side 2 (Television Live at Mothers 10/18/75): Marquee Moon, Friction, Torn Curtain, Breakin My Heart, Venus de Milo, Foxhole, Prove It, Poor Circulation, Little Johnny Jewel Pt III, Hard on Love (Soft)
      Format: 1/4 in. Audiocasssette
    - Television Live- CBGB December 30th 1976- Early Show, December 30, 1976 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0218)
      Side 1: Fire Engine, Venus de Milo, Elevation, Little Johnny Jewel, I Don't Care, Friction, Marquee Moon
      Side B: See No Evil, Prove it, Adventure*, Poor Circulation*, Oh Me Amore*, Knockin on Heaven's Door (), Kingdom Come- *battery Failure, () Skipped
    - Television Live CBGB July 30th, 1976 w/ Talking Heads, July 30, 1976 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0219)
      Side A: Fire Engine, Poor Circulation, Elevation, Venus de Milo, Foxhole, Knockin on Heaven's Door, Marquee Moon, See No Evil
      Side B: Prove it, Torn Curtain, Little Johnny Jewel, I Don't Care, Friction, Kingdom Come
      Container Annotation: MASTER, -P.D.-McKim-P.M.- Tom Verlaine - Vocal, Guitar; Richard Lloyd- Guitar, Backing Vocal; Billy Fecca - Drums; Fred Smith- Bass, Backing Vocal
    - Television June 10, 1978, My Father's Place (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0220)
      Side A: The Dreams Dream (6:00), Glory (3:45), Careful (3:00), Friction (4:20), Little Johnny Jewel (12:00), Ain't That Nothing 6:50?, Foxhole 4:50,
      Side B: Knockin' on Heaven's Door, Marquee Moon cut
    - Television Jan 25th 1976/ Talking Heads- Recorded by Monte at CBGB - both sets, January 25, 1976 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0221)
      Side A: Set I: Fire Engine, Venus de Milo, Little Johnny Jewel, A me Amore, Guiding Light, Marquee Moon. Set II: Prove It, Friction, Knockin' on Heaven's Door
      Side B: Torn Curtain, Let Me Out, Kingdom Come. TALKING HEADS: Artist's Only, First Week/Last Week..., I'm Not In Love, Building on Fire, [Track Unknown], Tentative Decisions. TELEVISION: Fire Engine
      Access CD available by appointment only. Please requests parts 1 and 2.
    - Television- My Father's Place 3-20-78, March 20, 1978 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0222)
      Side A: Fire Engine, Prove It, Foxhole, Poor Circulation, I Don't Care, Ain't that Nothin', Satisfaction -->
      Side B: Little Johnny Jewel, I See No Evil, Elevation, Friction, Marquee Moon
    - The Sex Pistols- The Heyday- Fact .30. A Factory Records Documentary Cassette, October 1980 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0223)
      Side A: Sid Vicious and Steve Jones. From interviews recorded during 1977 by Judy Vermorel
      Side B: Paul Cook, Johnny Rotten and Malcolm Maclaren's grandmother. Copyright on the interviews-Bondpen Publishing
    - Buzzcocks Sat Sept 1, '79 WPIX-FM, Irving Plaza, September 1, 1979 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0224)
      Content: WPIX-FM 9-1- 79 11:11pm- 12:05am, Irving Plaza/WPIX-FM 9-2-79 8:40-9:10pm
    - [Jorma] March 24. 1981- Lone Star cont'd/ [Brian Brain]- Hurrah Thursday April 2, 1981 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0225)
    - Bush Tetras, Pat Palladin CBGB March 2 1980 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0226)
    - Chelsea ICA London Nov 1976/ Sex Pistols Nov 15, 1976 "Notre Dame" London/ Damned Studio (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0227)
      Sides A and B: My Generation, Ready Steady Go, Anarchy, I Wanna Be Me, Seventeen, Pretty Vacant, No Feelings, Indian Summer, What Ya Gonna Do, Did You Do Wrong, Seventeen, Steppin Stone, Satellite, Problems, New York, Submission X/ See [yer] Tonight, Feel the Pain, I Fall
    - Tribute to the Stones July 24, 1978 Max's (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0228)
      Side A: Live with Me, Used to Love Her, Wild Horses, Tumblin Dice, Play with Fire, Make Love to You*, Under my Thumb[], Brown Sugar[], Jumpin Jack[], Suzy Q(), Round and Round()
      Side B: Cocksucker Blues, Last Time, Route 66, Boppin The Blues, Chinese Rocks, Dizzy Miss Lizzy, Can't Keep My Eyes on You